No way!
It's Matsuda.
Matsuda.
Where are you going?
Where did he go?
What's that?
Can you see it?
This is it.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh-shiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiight.
Oh-shiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiight.
Oh-shii...
Oh, shi... shi... shi...
Hello everyone, this is Konoka Matsuda!
I've just arrived at Kumamoto Airport after what seems like a long New Year's break!
According to the weather forecast, it was supposed to be sunny.
I hope it will be fine and I will enjoy myself!
I'm still in Kumamoto now!
Takachiho is in Miyazaki, but it's closer to Kumamoto!
That's why we flew from Kumamoto Airport!
Since we came all the way to Kumamoto!
We went to a restaurant where we could eat horse meat for lunch!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll wait for it!
The assortment has just arrived!
Looks delicious!
Can you see it?
Oh, watch out!
I almost did it!
Here it is!
Looks delicious!
Sakura Yukke and...
What's this?
It's some kind of horse!
Omoto, shinpufu, akami and yukke!
I wonder if it's akami...
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
Tender
Last, but not least, omatsuda!
Only horses
They laugh at me through their noses
It's time to use the Matsuda.
Bon appétit!
Delicious, this is also delicious
Matsuda
Oh Matsuda
Matsuda is useful for everyone
Matsuda.
How did you make it?
Here it is.
Normal Sakura Yukke
Rice
Matsuda
Matsuda.
Tomato.
You don't say anything private!
As soon as I turn on the video...
Cherry blossoms and natto
Sakura natto!
Good night!
Can I order this Sakura natto by itself?
Can I order it by itself?
sakura natto
Good night
I'll have a sakura natto snack.
It's hot.
I'm forcing the water.
I just put pressure on it like this.
Say it, say it, say it.
I'm home!
Sakura natto snacks have arrived!
It looks so delicious!
I'm counting on you!
Oh!
Is this what it looks like?
Let's mix it up!
Natto lovers won't be able to get enough of this.
Look at this.
Looks so good!
I'll try it.
elemental
Maybe natto people are stronger.
I see.
Yes, it's good.
It's delicious.
Okay, then.
Matsuda.
You already sound like an etch-a-sketch.
Yes, that's it.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Delicious.
We're on the border of Miyazaki. Welcome to Miyazaki.
Let's go!
I've just arrived at the inn in Takachiho.
It's a cheese bun with the sun written on it!
Ohisama cheese buns!
Bon appétit!
What's more, it's a Sora color! Could it be that the person from the sun made it?
Is it just a coincidence?
Bon appétit!
It's so crispy around the edges!
It's a cheese manju, but the outside is crunchy.
It says you can walk there in 3 minutes.
I'll get the kashikobon.
Three minutes. Let's go.
I'll open this one too.
Wait a minute, it says Thursday.
It says it's a holiday.
What? Which is what?
Tomorrow is Thursday?
What?
Tomorrow is Thursday.
I got it.
We're closing soon.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
What time?
5:00 p.m.
Oh, no, we close in 17 minutes.
Shall we go?
Yeah, let's go.
You should go.
Nice find.
Oh, there's only three of these in there.
No, three is three people.
I don't have time to eat right now.
This is not the time to eat.
I just realized.
That's good.
I'm glad you noticed.
I'm off.
It's raining a little bit.
Maybe this is it.
Are we there? Oh, there it is, there it is!
There's the uphill!
We've arrived at the sun-drenched cheese bun store!
This way.
Here it is!
Sunny Cheese Manju by Sorairo!
I'll go get permission to take a picture.
The beauty doesn't care how you name this one, now this schedule causesy to make a developer of anglechannel
It was a child.
Why is that good?
Let's have fun.
Good afternoon.
Thank you for coming.
Good morning.
It's the morning of the second day.
We have just arrived at Takachiho Shrine.
I would like to pay my respects.
I would like to eat meat sushi!
New School No. 10, No. 11.
Where is your restaurant?
My restaurant.
It's the restaurant at number 13.
That's the one.
Thank you very much.
Time comes and goes, and thoughts gradually come to us. Happiness gathers before us.
But if you don't think things through carefully, you may have regrets and lose money.
So we must think carefully
Wishes may surprise you, but panic will make them come true
You mustn't be in a hurry...
I wonder if this is the year of the Last Succession
Marriage CHEERING
Next, we came to Amano-Iwato Shrine, where Amaterasu is enshrined.
Can you guess? Then! The West Main Shrine of Amano-Iwato Shrine.
I would like to pay my respects to the birds.
The light of the sky view is in brewer force brand,
F-55E nossos album is my daily station,
I would be very happy if you could give it to me!
Amazing.
I heard that if you pile up stones like this, your wish will come true.
I'm going to try it too!
I'll collect the stones first.
I'll try with these 5 stones.
Here's the pressure point
It's easier to fill the mouth
And...
Is this the big one?
Oh!
Not this one. I just happened to put my wrist here.
Put this daddy's wrist here.
Oh!
It's done!
This daddy's challenge
What a lot of big stuff!
Yeah, I didn't expect that.
Oh!
We can come back again.
Parent-child set
Mom's challenge
Oh, it's done!
Oh, this is it!
This is amazing!
What fun!
Various people's works
Here they are!
Here you go.
Cheer up!
This is the teaser video of the fourth term students.
We've come to the sea of Ulus.
The Holy Land.
Wow!
It's shaped like this.
Can you find this place?
It's beautiful.
Sunshine.
Can we go?
Here's your chance! Come on!
I found it right here.
Can you see it?
Oh, we made it!
It says "Reservoir Movie Shooting Location".
This must be it.
Pilgrimage to the Holy Land
This is it.
Here
here
Good morning.
It's the third morning.
Just now.
Oh, we're here already?
I think so.
MRT, Miyazaki Broadcasting Co.
Hinaya will be on air from January 11.
I was just in the neighborhood.
Can you see it here?
Ta-da!
Wow!
It says "MRT" on it.
Vacation.
Is this the antenna?
I'll put it on your head.
MRT.
Miyazaki Broadcasting.
Are you sure?
It's right here.
I'll see you at Hyugaizaka.
Please start at 26 minutes.
We're here in front of the Uto shrine.
I'm going to pay my respects now.
We are waiting for you.
I'm going to throw a ball of luck.
Good luck!
Over.
Oh! Oh! There it is! Nice!
Oh! Oh! It's got him! Nice!
One more.
I put a little more in.
It's all gone.
One more time.
A little more.
Too much pull.
I got one in.
Two. Two. Two.
We're in the water, right?
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
We did it!
Ohkun's counting!
Oh!
He's finding all kinds of shrines
What do you got?
There's something in here.
There's a foreign store in here.
It's true.
Seven Lucky Gods No. 49.
It's like this, isn't it?
Wow, I've never seen this before.
Dragon Tenryu
Oh no, it was written here.
Kichi.
Kichi, I knew it!
It's good luck to be a dragon.
Don't just wait... be bold and try.
Yes, it says that.
It's the very essence of life.
Open up, now, and whatever difficulties you face will turn into blessings.
Will turn into a blessing.
Oh, that's good.
But happiness is the first thing it says.
Yes, sir.
Congratulations.
Blessing.
Yes, sir
We've arrived at Miyazaki Bougainvillea Airport
I flew from Kumamoto Airport when I arrived.
I'm going back from Miyazaki Bougainvillea Airport
As you can see here, it's called the Sunshine of Japan
I was very happy to be able to come to Miyazaki Prefecture, which is called the "Sunshine of Japan" as you can see here.
I hope to be able to come again with the members of Hyuuga-saka and
I hope one day I will be able to come here again with the members of Hyuga-saka and everyone in the sun!
Thank you very much, it was a lot of fun!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching!